Weeeeeeeeeeeee!!!!
Yaa!
-Next one!
-Please.
Is it true that you tried to push that girl down?
What are you talking about.
Our firm can do whatever...
...but I cannot work with you.
Sorry. Because I introduced you to that man...
...I have hurt you.
I took this.
You... I will return this.
Let go!
No, you let go!
Give it back!
(Matsushima Kenichiro - business development department, Frontier Constructions)
Teach me, master!
I'm not a master, but what?
(Yamazaki Ryosuke - son of sales manager Yamazaki)
When I face the opponent my mind is restless.
What should I do?
-Empty your mind!
-Empty your mind?
Yes, you have to enter a state of calm emptiness.
Can you do that?
(Are you stupid?)
No, it's difficult.
-Idiot!
-12.
-Really an idiot!
-13.
-Don't call someone an idiot.
-That's right.
You said it 13 times now.
I have to say it otherwise he doesn't get it.
I think it was good, what Ken-chan did.
(Machida Yoshino - sales person, Agna)
But for such a woman.
It wasn't for this Narumi-san, right?
Maybe you wanted to make your point.
You didn't think about your own gain or loss
but you wanted to protect what you hold important.
Maybe something like this.
Mmh, that's it.
Thank you for understanding.
That's it!
Here you go.
(Kumazawa Shiro, business development department, Frontier Constructions)
Meat skewers for you.
I didn't order them.
-You did.
I did.
Hey, Hide. Tell us something interesting.
(Kusaka Hideki, business development department, Frontier Constructions)
Huh?
Ah, yes!
Recently Yamanishi from sales...
and Kaori-chan from assessment...
had a date in Yokohama...
[Kurita Narumi]
Who is it?
It's not that woman.
Huh? Ah.
Ignore her, ignore her!
[Kurita Narumi]
Then what?
When they walked in the Yamashita park...
...they apparently met an alien.
What?
-How did they know it was an alien?
-It spoke to them and...
...said to them...
Crap! Switch it off.
No, I'll tell her:
"Don't call me!"
-Hello?
-Help me.
What? Hello?
What happened?
Please! Come quick.
Come where?
What did she say?
"Help me" and hung up.
Isn't she only making fun of you?
No, it didn't sound like that.
Anyway, leave her alone.
Then what?
-Ah, you want to know.
-I wanna know.
-The alien.
-Kumazawa-san.
-I'm Kumazawa.
-It was...
-Yes.
-with Kaori-chan...
-Again?
-...in Yokohama.
-Yes, it was a date.
You are connected to AU voice mail.
Sorry, I'll be right back.
Hey! Do you have an obligation to help that woman?
Not an obligation but there's something called sympathy.
What are you saying.
I cannot leave someone who begs for help alone.
Sorry.
-What an idiot.
-14.
I come in.
Hey are you there?
Hey what's wrong?
(Kurita Narumi - Freeter)
Huh?
Co...
Co?
Cockroach.
What?
There was a cockroach.
Please! Quick! Do something quick! Quick!
A cockroach, a normal cockroach?
Are there other ones?
You called me for that?
I can't stand cockroaches.
When I just see them...
No no...
you needed help for that?
They fly, the cockroaches.
When I was a child, one flew
into my mouth.
Since then it's...now quick.
Here, take this. Somewhere there.
Listen, cockroaches are animals...
...which will survive even after
the extinction of mankind.
So when you kill them
at least show some respect...
There!
And?
Got it!
Not there, flush it in the toilet.
And this?
Throw it away.
Is that all?
Thank you for your trouble.
You can leave.
Huh?
Something else?
I had trouble coming here.
-What? You want to talk to me?
-Not at all.
I was out drinking with my friends.
And because of you...
No, I shouldn't blame people.
Anyway...anyway...
You will not call me anymore.
Is this clear? You understand!
Good bye!
And when another cockroach comes...
(Yamazaki Yoshiki - Sales manager at the business development department, Frontier Constructions)
Yo!
Here!
Ah, thanks.
I am really sorry. Again I caused you trouble.
That's your character, can't be helped.
But is it okay? Like this.
[Honmachi Garden Hills, Construction Draft]
What is this?
A construction project for an apartment
in Honmachi is facing the resistance of the residents.
Next Monday there is a meeting with the residents...
...but chief Shiozaki has come down with the flu.
-You should do it.
-Huh?
But I don't know anything about this subject.
Your role in this meeting is...
...to become a sandbag and take the residents' scolding.
If you do this, I'll bring you back to the business development department.
-Really?
-You wanna try?
-Yes, let me do it.
-Right.
Ah. Kumazawa is a bit down recently.
-Do you know if anything happened?
-Dunno.
Like today.
((The second one from the left))
((Yes, yes!))
Are you reporting your date?
Ah, you, are you together with Sasaki-kun?
Boss, this is sexual harrassment.
It's all in jest.
(Kuwata Sachiko - Frontier Constructions)
Please don't talk about love affairs at work.
I'm off.
Sorry.
Is he suffering because of a woman?
Actually, there is a woman he likes.
He wanted my assistance but it's gotten a bit nebulous.
-If you're a friend, you help him.
-I understand.
I'll prepare an arrangement for a date.
-Ah, see ya.
-Thank you very much.
Because I love you.
This means you will listen to everything I say?
Of course. I will follow you to hell.
(Kayashima Yukie - Aspiring Actress)
Ah, I'm glad, that I hear such words from you.
Then what will you do for me?
(note: She starts to fall into Akita dialect)
-Haah, I mispronounce.
-I will bungle the audition again.
-But...it's pretty funny.
-This is a serious drama.
Hmmm.
A package for you!
Yes.
Huh? What?
Isn't Narumi here?
Right now she's not.
Then I'll wait here.
Hi.
Hold it right there!
Hold on!
Hello.
I heard your ringtone. You are somewhere close.
-When were you released?
-Yesterday. For good behavior.
Congrats.
It was your fault, that they caught me.
-Hmm, but I didn't do it on purpose.
-It was tough in prison.
-Take responsibility.
-Responsibility?
Be my girl.
As compensation for destroying my life.
-Naa.
-What's that "naa"?
I see, you have a new lover?
I have.
Who is it?
None of your business.
You get on my nerves. You go away!
- will kill you.
-Try if you can do it.
Fuck! Come out!
Yoshino-chan, look look!
I bought this talisman at the Shiranui shrine.
The effect is great.
Yoshiko-san bought this and soon she got married.
-It's great.
-Hmm.
I'll give you a little bit of the effect.
(Morioka Kumi - Shop Manager, Agna)
-Here.
-Thank you.
-What shall I do?
-Joy.
Boss, there is "Prayer for an easy childbirth"
written on it.
What?
[Prayer for an easy childbirth]
-Why?
-Good afternoon.
Ah, good afternoon.
There must be a marriage before a childbirth.
-That's tough.
-Would you like a cup of tea?
Don't worry.
I just came along.
I see.
Umm...this.
[The Lovers from Notting Hill]
-Go with someone.
-Who's someone?
This is...
((it would be boring without a kind of person like him.))
((I'm glad that I spoke to him.))
...the man you like.
-Who is it?
-Don't ask me that.
Ah, Ken-chan.
-Oh, you're here.
-What do you want?
Look...this.
I had 2 tickets left: Haoden.
-Go with someone.
-Who is someone?
Who should it be?
-Huh? a..and these?
-Kumazawa-san just gave me them.
What? Ah..I see..I see.
You are doing really well without my assistance.
It's not like that.
Ah, sorry.
[Kurita Narumi]
Get a life!
Don't call me anymore. Enough!
Well see ya. Enjoy yourselves.
-I'm looking for a guy called Matsushima.
-May I ask your name?
Not your business!
Just get Matsushima here!
Go...
No no...
What is the matter?
-Are you Matsushima?
-No, but what do you want from him?
Hello, what's up?
Someone like Yakuza guy?
-Who?
-I want to know that from you.
Wait a sec.
And? What did he do?
When I said I would call the police
he left reluctantly.
He seems to bear quite a grudge against you.
I don't recall anyone bearing a
grudge against me.
Hmmm...now that you said it, he didn't know
your face.
Which means that I haven't met him.
-Maybe...
-That woman!?
No one else could bring me that kind of trouble.
-We met the other day.
-Hello.
-Where is that girl?
-Umm...Kurita Narumi
-She went to work.
-Ah, I see.
Work? What work?
Thanks! Take this!
-What happened?
-The rabbit...
What kind of marketing job?
Why are you doing such a job.
Why? I have to earn a living.
And it's quite popular among the children.
Other than that, do have any acquaintances that include...
...a Yakuza-like guy with thin eyes.
-Ah, he already went, huh?!
-I knew it was you.
He came to my firm but didn't meet me.
-Glad you didn't meet him.
-What's all that? Explain!
Hmm, that...
((Someone!))
((Shut up or I break your arm!))
((I see. I see.))
((Matsushima Kenichiro.))
((Is this your boyfriend?))
((Hm hmm.))
((Hmm.))
((Get a life!))
((Don't call me anymore. Enough!))
((This bastard!))
-That was then.
-You pissed him off.
When you get me into such a situation, at least warn me.
And?
What's your relationship with him?
He is mad at me, yet he is still attached to me.
-Why is he mad at you?
-When we were together...
...I once went to his appartment
while he was away.
They didn't look healthy so...
I put them out into the sun on the balcony.
Maybe it was...cannabis?
Yeah, something like that.
I discovered something that looks like cannabis
Good work.
Narumi.
That's why he was mad at me.
Why were you together with such a man?
I don't remember now. That was two years ago.
A relationship isn't such a simple thing.
First you should learn about each other...
Is this a lecture?
Anyway, because I don't know him...
...explain that to him.
I cannot do that.
-Why?
-I said that the cannabis thing ...
...was an idea fed by you.
Why did you say something like that?
To distract him from me. I had no choice.
Don't you consider other people's trouble?
He's a guy who's unpredictable when he's mad. Be careful.
I have to go now.
See ya.
I'll take this one.
15,000 Yen please.
Yes. Wait a little.
[Stop being such a stupid wrongdoer.]
And what about the man who came today?
Ah...it's alright. Sorry about that.
Hey! Did you completely break off your relationship
with that woman.
-Mmmh. Sort of.
-Gee.
-Ah, yes. Hide, that one.
-Yes.
-Here.
-What's that?
You have a meeting with residents, don't you?
I gathered various things about past trouble with residents.
It might be a little help.
Thanks.
Come back to the business development department.
We are all waiting for you.
Thanks.
Idiot. You did such a thing.
You have my support for Yoshino.
Wha..?
What are you whispering?
Ah, it's nothing.
What?
It's nothing.
Amusing, isn't it?
The funniest thing I heard in the last 3 days.
But will he be alright?
I think he's someone who can overcome anything.
Hmm.
Since you said that, are you attracted to him?
(Yabe Norio - Owner of the Bar Rybeus)
No way, he's so stressful.
And what about him?
I'm probably the only person in the world
who irritates him the most.
For a moment I thought a rival has appeared.
If he gets stabbed and dies, maybe will it be my fault?
Hmm. Not maybe, it will definitely be.
If that happens then please become a buddha.
Haha, that's your charm.
-Hey, Chika-chan, treat her with another one.
-Yes.
The appartment resident Imai Hisae-san...
...was stabbed with a sharp object and
died of blood loss.
The suspect is the unemployed Tanioka Noboru who lives...
...in the Suginami district.
(Matsuhima Mina - Kenichiro's younger sister)
Supposedly the suspect Tanioka Noboru's
target was Hisae-san's sister Kimiko-san.
When he broke in and Kimiko-san was absent...
...he stabbed Hisae-san in her place.
Contrary to the police investigation
the suspect Tanioka testified that...
...to relieve his grudge...
...it wasn't important whom he stabbed.
He seems to not show any signs of remorse.
Hey.
It's sunday, it's okay to slack off.
I'm not complaining about that.
Do you mind taking days off from your job?
-Heh?!
-Go to our parents for a while.
-Huh? Why.
-You have to.
I don't understand that.
Can't you listen to your brother?
Why do you come up with this now?
Yes yes... yes yes yes.
Yes..yes.
Wait a sec.
Hey!
Good afternoon.
I made Kinpira. Would you like some?
(Yamazaki Tamami - Wife of sales manager Yamazaki)
They look tasty. Thank you.
Thanks.
Anything wrong?
-He was a bit strange.
-Don't say that.
What happened? You can tell us.
-From one thing to the next.
-I am deeply sorry.
That's why you wanted me to return home.
-Is he that dangerous?
-No, it's not a big deal.
-You are scared.
-Huh?
But Sakagami-san promised to do what he can.
If we leave it to him, it should be alright.
-Who is this Sakagami-san?
-He was a fellow student of mine.
Now he's a detective at the Metropolitan Police.
Before we got married, we competed for her.
-And you won?
-Seems so.
That was once.
But he isn't resentful?
He's not that kind of person.
According to him...
...what this guy called Kunieda has committed
were lots of threats and interfering with a public official in the line of duty.
Right now Sakagami's detectives
are going to his apartment.
That's good for you, onii-chan.
Umm.
Oh! Sakagami.
Hello. I'm sorry. How did it go?
Eh?! I see. I got it. Thank you.
-What's going on?
-He said that Kunieda has disappeared.
Eh?!
He disappeared in anticipation that the police might come after him.
Then does it mean he is targeting Matsushima-kun?
Well, I don't know about it.
You might need to stay at home to take extra precaution.
No, I can't do that.
But the guy, Kunieda, has some criminal record beside cannabis, right?!
I can't stay at home because I will have the residents' meeting tomorrow.
Ah, I was thinking to go to see the actual place today.
It's not really necessary to visit the place.
You just need to bow down at the meeting.
I don't want to be rude to the residents.
Most importantly is your physical safety.
That's right. I'll give you another chance.
Stay at home today.
Because you, Kumazawa and the others...
have worked hard to get me back...
-it's not the time to run and hide.
-You pretend to be tough.
I don't pretend. I just proceed logically.
Which means I'm off.
Hey!
Ah.
Hello.
Oh, Yoshino, what's up?
-I am angry.
-What?
-Why?
-Because...
Sorry that I dragged you to this place.
-Hum.
-Cheer up.
Why didn't you tell me that you
are facing such a danger?
Kumazawa-san told me about it.
-You would only be worried.
-Probably.
Ah, here it is.
-Say.
-Hmm.
You are not Narumi-san's boyfriend,...
...you didn't know her two years ago.
If you tell Kunieda that, won't that help?
But I don't even know where he is.
-Why don't you leave a message on his phone?
-Hmm.
If you don't even do that in this danger, you are like an idiot.
Ah, I dunno.
-Do you want to protect Narumi-san?
-Huh?
Because you want to protect her you
draw the danger to yourself.
-Why should I.
-Then why?
If you wanted to do the residents' meeting properly
you normally would shake off the sparks which fall on you.
Hmm. I don't run away just because it's dangerous...
...and I want to do the things I have to do properly.
You can call me an idiot for that.
Then...
...if something happened to me would you protect me?
Of course I would.
-Shin-chan, it's time for supper.
-Yes.
Bye bye.
-Umm...is Matsushima-san there?
-Any help.
-I'm fine.
-You know Narumi, right?
-Yes, that's right.
Tell her this:
I might go to prison once more.
Ah...is your name Kunieda?
Bye.
What? He came to you? Why?
He sounded like he is up to something.
Once with resolve.
-Is it okay if you stay away.
-Why not?
If you say so.
Don't say to me later,
"Why didn't you tell me?"
Just in case I called you. See ya.
Good afternoon.
Welcome.
Business development department.
Umm..is Matsushima-san there?
Matsushima-san isn't here
-Where is he?
-Ah!
Aren't you the one who visited Matsushima-san recently?
Just tell me where he is.
I cannot do that.
Oh well. He is in a dangerous situation.
If anything happens to him it's your fault.
What?
Ladies and gentleman,
you came here even though...
you were very busy. I deeply appreciate that.
I hereby open...
...the residents' meeting of Honmachi garden hills.
There are no legal problems
with the construction plans,
the architectural basis is...
What we want to hear is not that
type of speech.
Will these apartments...
...have an influence on our life or not.
We want an actual discussion about that.
But this might be a subjective question.
-Are you dodging the problem?
-No, I don't intend to do that.
We are not just following the basic laws...
...we are being attentive not to disturb more of the environment you are living in.
We would like to explain it with the best of intentions...
...and we would like you to have a much better understanding.
You think that bowing solves everything?!
-You are dodging!
-That's right!
I appreciate it if you understand, please.
-Why don't you say anything?
-Err...yes.
Please answer.
Will there be an influence on our life or not.
Will the apartments cause us problems or not?
An influence...
[Manual : how to deal a residents' meeting]
[Do not tell details and just bow down]
An influence...
An influence exists.
I think it will cause you problems.
What's he saying?
Is he serious?
According to these data...
...the planning commissionary tried extremely hard...
but with the building of the apartments,
the estates to the north will lose 1.5 hours
of sunshine on average.
But in exchange, if the appartmets are built
there will come new families. Total of 43 new families.
-What does it matter?
-It matters.
Yesterday I walked in this neighborhood.
I felt that this is a really friendly neighborhood.
I heard a mother calling her child for supper...
...it's been a long time for me since I saw that.
In this wonderful town...
...you might have 43 new families as neighbors.
Would you please accept them?
More people living might cause...
...chafe, inconvenience or something may happen with the change.
However, does it have to be zero of them?
Having new residents might give...
...some hard time for each other.
But there must be a lot of happiness...
...sharing with new people, I think.
Isn't that life?!
Getting close to a person you thought that you wouldn't like...
...but the person becomes a precious one someday.
I think that it's possible that it might happen.
[Stop being such a stupid wrongdoer.]
Just a little...
...would you please have the courage to open your hearts?
[I will be waiting for you with mom. You can come back any time. -Your father.]
Was what I said naive?
You...are naive.
Naive but...
that's not bad.
Huh?
Up to now there was nobody
who didn't run away...
...and explained properly.
What do you think?
Thank you very much.
It's okay.
May I offer my help?
Thank you very much.
Good morning.
-Good morning.
We will have a meeting for a new project.
-Oh.
Thank you for waiting.
And what did this Kunieda do after that?
He returned directly to his parents' farm.
You always liked...
...growing plants.
Seems so.
He's just the right person for the job.
-It's because of Matsushima.
-He is a really weird guy.
I need to talk to you.
-May I leave my seat?
-It's okay.
What is it?
You are pretending to be a nice person, and it feels good to you, right?!
Sometimes, it is nice to be just the two of us.
That girl likes you.
-Do your best!
-I like you...
-Umm...
-He puts up a big front but...
...can't see himself.
-Promises are for breaking.
-You are done here.
Why didn't you leave me alone.