[Construction site]
(Matsushima Kenichiro - Business development department, Frontier Constructions)
Do you have a letter for Yamanishi Sawako-san?
From America, right?
Yes.
It is the right address here.
I heard that it'll arrive today and waited here.
I'll take it.
Ah, hello.
The letter for Granny has arrived.
How is she?
She's dying?
I'll come at once.
Granny!
Matsushima-san,
you came late.
Granny, the letter from your grandson Ma-kun.
It arrived from America.
Granny!
Who is he?
Someone from the construction firm.
Granny.
Ma-kun sent the letter and didn't know...
...that her house would be demolished.
Why does someone from the construction firm do this much?
Granny, hold out!
Granny!
The Granny!
Granny.
Granny, look! The letter from Ma-kun.
Thank you.
Who are you?
Not so important.
One year later
Good work.
Excuse me.
We talked on the phone about it.
Can you do that please.
Hey! You asked them to make...
(Kumazawa Shiro - Business development department, Frontier Constructions)
...a window frame there?
I haven't heard of such a thing.
The owner called me this morning.
Why this now?
Come with me.
If there is a window, one can just about see Mount Fuji.
From here? Mount Fuji?
Ah! Indeed.
The president wants to see Mount Fuji
from his office everyday.
But to hold down
clients' extravagances is our job, too.
The president remembers
from childhood...
...climbing Mt.Fuji with his deceased dad.
We can grant his wish.
Do you know how much work is involved in making a window?
America sent people to the moon, Japan can't.
Do you know why this is so?
A matter of technology, funding,...
No!
It's because America decided to send people to the moon.
You with your character bring people into trouble!
My bad!
It's bad!
Wait, wait, wait.
Let's keep cool, the two of you.
(Kusaka Hideki - Business development department, Frontier Constructions)
Who do you think is right?
Huh? If you ask me like that...
Anyway, I am sick of working with you!
These are my words!
Don't think you can beat me in staring!
I know. Do as you like.
Thanks! You understand me.
It's always like that.
Excuse me. Can you arrange for
making a window there?
Please.
Ah yes! Listen.
Is it okay with the plan tonight?
Ah, this.
Yoshijo Real Estate's 30th anniversary party.
No, after that. The get-together with Yoshino
and others.
You haven't forgotten that?
I told you I wanted to make things clear tonight.
It came out.
Then don't do a get-together, get a date.
You say so? I need your assistance.
What a poor fellow.
And? What should I do?
Somehow praise me.
Ah, I understand. Then I...
...talk about how you slipped on the
fresh concrete the other day.
Hahaha...don't mess with me!
Here. Here.
(Kurita Narumi - Freeter)
(note: freeter = part time worker)
Here.
Still so many.
Miss, what...
What's this?
Free tissues.
I don't need that many.
Of course.
You can go now, go!
I don't want to.
Don't worry, quick quick!
What are you doing?
This man held me up.
Who?
What?
You are fired.
I know.
What?
Today's pay.
You haven't even worked one hour. Nothing!
Huh?
Nothing.
Then some of these, please.
Don't touch them.
Stingy!
What a woman.
Yeah.
Nothing to do.
No money.
I'm hungry.
[Party Invitation]
What? You can't do that.
Can't you do something about it?
But I am busy with the inventory.
So can I skip our get-together tonight?
(Machida Yoshino - Sales Person, Agna)
You can't.
Why?
No, please.
I am your friend.
Why should I?
Because...
...I introduced you to an inexpensive firm
for your parents' home renovation.
I can't refuse then.
Yep. I beg you.
Under one condition.
Bring a match for my shop manager.
(Morioka Kumi - Shop Manager, Agna)
For Kumi-san?
Recently her desire to marry has gotten strong.
Right now she's tracing the marriage line on her palm with a pen.
When I am her age will I be the same?
You will find a good partner for sure.
Huh? What do you mean?
Ah. No, nothing.
See you. Please come.
Here it is.
We get out before 8 o'clock.
I know.
So you mention to Yoshino-chan...
...that I got a prize from the chief manager
and that I did a two-base at the baseball tournament.
Aren't there greater deeds?
What?
Welcome.
Good evening.
Kumazawa from Frontier Constructions.
What?
That's strange.
It's gone.
Excuse me...
...we lost an invitation.
Is this a problem?
What is your name?
Frontier Constructions, Matsushima.
Yes. If you are Matsushima-san...
...a representative came for you.
A representative?
Who?
Who is it?
A young woman in a red plaid shirt.
Champagne please.
She? Is she from our firm?
Dunno.
Tenpura is served.
Please.
Kumazawa-kun, you here?
Ah, it's been a while.
Glad you came. I want to introduce you to someone.
Excuse me, but...
...are you the representative for Matsushima-san from
Frontier Constructions?
Huh? Ah..yes.
I am Matsushima.
Ah..hello!
Hello..now who are you?
It's not the situation to tell you my name.
Simply tell me your name.
Kurita Narumi. Hello.
Why are you using the invitation of someone else.
I thought maybe I'm invited.
No. It's my name, isn't it?
The invitation letter fell from heaven...
...so maybe God invited me.
I dropped it.
Are you God?
No!
Anyway, you used someone else's invitation
to eat and drink.
Towards me and towards the host of the party,
it's doubly rude.
I almost ate up. Shall I return it?
It's okay. You don't have to.
That's not the problem.
Then what should I do?
First it would be appropriate to show some regret.
In a spontaneous impulse,
one might do things like that...
Won't you stop eating?
Huh?
What?
Ouch. Ouch. It hurts.
Don't fake an illness.
Ouch. Ouch. Ouch.
Are you serious?
Hold on?
Is this real?
Are you okay?
Hold out a little.
Excuse me. She doesn't feel well.
Could you call an ambulance?
Yes.
But Touto hospital is right over there.
You might go there directly.
Yes.
Thank you.
Let's go.
Don't use a cell phone in the hospital.
I'm sorry.
Where is he?
How is she?
Where has she been up to now?
In the assembly room of the hotel over there.
She shows an intense digestive reaction.
In other words she simply ate too much.
Huh?
Take care.
That's from eating too much.
Cause for once I sneaked into a party...
...I wanted to eat two meals at once.
Don't you have any money?
Like 300 yen.
Why do you only have 300 yen?
It's complicated why people are poor...
...moreso than why some are rich.
But a single young woman...
...can earn her living somehow.
Dirty.
You mean that I become a prostitute?
Pardon?
I didn't mean that.
And you are working in a construction firm?
Are you building houses?
To be exact I make the construction plans.
I once built a plastic model from Himeji castle.
The donjon from Himeji castle is
architecturally speaking
a compound donjon, the most intricate structure.
No one wants to hear that.
You started it.
How will I get along tomorrow?
There's also the hospital bill.
Here.
Huh? Is it okay?
Yeah.
I'll give it back. Give me your number.
Don't worry about it.
Ah! Crap!
Bye!
Don't do that ever again.
Good evening.
Welcome.
One beer.
From the tap.
-Sorry. Sorry.
-Finally you came.
O yes. You are late.
These two are already drunk.
And? How did it go?
Not yet. I didn't do anything.
I need your assistance I said.
Let's do it now.
Too late. I'm already drunk.
What are you whispering?
Ah nothing.
Are you having fun?
We talked about Kumi's spouse hunting.
I wanna marry.
One more.
Me too.
Ah, my marriage line disappears.
Do you need a pen?
Thanks.
-Thank you.
-I might marry you.
Huh?
My ex-boyfriend...
I should have married him.
Regretting now?
No use crying over spilt milk.
Like this guy.
What about me?
You were already accepted
by Dainihon Construction
You had the chance to enter a top 5 business.
Don't talk about it.
What? I didn't know that.
You heard about the Dainichi cover-up scandal?
I heard about it.
That company forged the contents of a survey.
They developed something that harmed the ecosystem.
He knew that and refused.
What an idiot.
I didn't want to enter a firm that forges data.
But it's your childhood dream...
...to construct big buildings and bridges.
For this type of projects, you need to work for
a large construction firm.
You think you can build big stuff with our firm?
I can.
How?
I will make our firm able to do that. Yes.
You are really...
What? Stop it.
Really an idiot.
-Here you go.
-Thank you.
Let's have a toast.
On our future.
Cheers!
Let's drink today! One more beer.
[Frontier Constructions - Staff housing]
Ah, I drank too much.
Uh, I drank too much.
(Matsuhima Nami, Kenichiro's younger sister )
While you are a bummer, don't drink that much.
I am not a bummer. I have a part-time job.
Hey, don't fall asleep again.
Sit up straight.
It's okay.
Your sermon will be long.
For what have you been supported through university?
Our mother is worried.
I can't help it.
The firm went bankrupt.
You shouldn't have entered such a firm.
Anyway, don't make our parents worry.
Come on, make me breakfast.
It's hopeless.
Oops!
But it's surely good that you have at least a part-time job.
That's uncommon. You agree with me.
There exist much worse women than you.
Huh? Who? Who is it?
Worry about yourself.
You are like air.
No shadow, no form, like air.
To be frank...
...I want to break up.
I can't imagine a future together with you.
Another audition?
You are awake?
Can you accompany me a bit?
(Kayashima Yukie - Aspiring Actress)
Hmm, well...
Why do you leave? Don't you like me anymore?
No, I like you. But I have to go.
(Yukie speaks Akita dialect)
If we stay together, it will not work out.
Am I mispronouncing a little?
No.
Really?
Not a little, a lot.
Huh? When I am tense I mispronounce.
Isn't it okay with your dialect?
It's the way you are.
I can't do that. The role is a
young lady born in Tokyo.
Keep trying.
A friend told me I don't prosper because...
...a poverty spirit might reside here.
A poverty spirit?
Maybe me...ha ha ha.
It's not funny.
It's been half a year now
since you came here.
Time flies, doesn't it?
I beg you. Please leave.
If you are that serious...
...I'll consider it.
Please.
Yes.
-Then I'm off.
-Yes. Bye.
Really looks like a poverty spirit is here.
No way Yamaguchi-sensei will approve this budget.
He's famous for his gorgeous designs.
You should have asked him to design the interior
of super upper class apartments.
But it's central to this project...
...to ask him to do middle class apartments.
It's pointless.
Being restrained by a tight budget is below his league.
We don't know if we don't ask.
Completely pointless.
I understand what Matsushima-san says, but...
Shut up!
Sorry.
-Hi.
-Yamaguchi-sensei.
Sorry. Do you mind the budget?
The budget you proposed...
(Yamazaki Yoshiki - Sales manager of the business development department)
...was accepted by Yamaguchi-sensei.
What? Really?
Is it alright?
Isn't it troubling you?
To deliver even under ...
...a limited budget, can't a pro do that?
Matsushima-kun, you said so?
You came to my office everyday
and begged me that eagerly...
...so I can't withdraw from it. Cause I'm a pro.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
I'll introduce Yamaguchi-sensei
to the president.
Yes.
See y'all.
Thank you very much.
He gave in to you.
I knew that he'd understand me.
Right!
Since Yamaguchi-sensei will work for this,
the client wants...
...to make this space a bit wider.
Is this feasible?
That's tricky.
I know that it's tricky but...
could you at least try.
Matsushima-san.
A visitor.
Who?
A visit during work from
such a person?
(Kuwata Sachiko - Frontier Constructions)
What does that mean?
Such a person?
Why are you here?
Show more reaction.
Why did you come to my company.
And how did you know?
The party invitation was for
Matsushima Kenichiro, Frontier Constructions.
What do you want?
About the money I borrowed.
Ah, you came to return it?
Exceptionally honest.
Huh?
I borrowed 5,000 yen.
So what?
Aren't 5,000 yen sort of incomplete?
When you add another 5,000 yen they
perfectly add up to 10,000 yen.
You want me to lend you another 5,000 yen?
You can say so.
I refuse.
Stingy.
I'm not stingy.
I hate such piecemeal.
I don't have any duty to lend you more money.
Not a duty but there's kindness.
I don't care! Go home.
The lunch break is soon.
Is this a party?
You will overeat again.
When I can eat as much as I like...
...I'd like to eat for one week in advance.
Listen. In life you have to...
There are men who get women around
with this type of sermons.
Don't mix things up.
Was your character always like that?
To say what is rightful.
That's not my intention.
Maybe it's the influence of my passed away dad.
My dad was a straightforward man. Itadakimasu.
But isn't it tiresome to not even be a little crooked?
There's a limit to being crooked.
Am I that crooked?
You are snaky.
That's my individuality.
Try living seriously and honestly.
You'll feel better and your future will be bright.
As a couple we would fail a matching test horribly.
How should I care?
When did your father die?
When I was in fourth grade.
Good people die early.
And? You don't have any work?
There is no suitable work.
There are lots of job offers from
supermarkets and restaurants.
I am suited for more creative work.
Creative?
Have you done such work?
Hmm. Like cameraman or illustrator.
Ah, Really?
I freelanced a lot.
And also as writer.
Maybe our public relations department has such work.
Something great, glamorous and well paid, please.
Don't be so spoilt. Did I even say...
that I'll help you find work.
If you don't feel like it then don't mention it.
Well, I could ask.
When you say that I cannot refuse.
What am I doing?
What are you doing?
For take home.
Don't do that.
Then what will I eat tonight?
What? You could have given me that earlier.
You don't need to give it back.
I'll give it back.
You don't need to.
I'll do.
Don't come and give it back.
I will come.
I just came by your store.
And thought: why not have lunch together?
Last night while being drunk, I didn't say anything weird?
It's okay.
But the two of you are good friends, huh?
Me and?
Ken-chan and you.
Ah.
We entered the firm at the same time.
During a training course we had a huge argument.
A huge argument? Why?
When I disagreed openly with the instructor...
...he said that this is rude.
But after that we strangely fit together.
Umm.
While we are at it how did you meet him?
He hasn't told you?
No.
By chance one can say...
((It's been a one-way street here for a long time.))
((I'm telling you that I didn't see the one-way sign.))
((Ah, you were careless.))
((Show me your driver's license.))
((Please...))
((Excuse me, but...
... the sign is really hard to see.))
((I beg your pardon?))
((I have been thinking...
... you should not be policing here.))
((Why don't you stay over there and warn people at the entrance?))
((What are you telling me?))
((That is really for the citizens.))
((It's okay.))
((It's not okay.))
((I'm sorry.))
((You wanted to protect the citizens,...
... that's why you became a policeman, right?))
((Well....))
((Isn't it true?))
((Excuse us.))
((Here, please.))
((It's still hard to see.))
((A little more please.))
((Ah, that's it, over there.))
That's what happened.
Why hasn't he told you?
It's not an unusual thing to him.
But it had an impact on me.
He is silly, isn't he?!
He is silly.
However, it would be boring without someone like him.
That's why...
((Now we can see it well. Yes, it's perfect.))
((Thank you very much.))
((Thank you very much. Excuse me.))
((Excuse me.))
You spoke to him first.
I felt that I would never meet someone like him again.
I'm glad that I spoke to him.
Ah... I just remember that I have something to do.
I'm sorry. Would you eat lunch by yourself?
Sure.
Then, see you.
See you.
Good work.
Who might it be?
Ah, good work today.
Ah, good work.
Listen to this.
A girl came.
Um?
Eh?!
Really?
Really.
Hey.
Um?
Who was the girl?
Eh?!
She was a quite cute girl.
Hey!
Come on, who was it?
The girl from the party last night.
You...
What....
Are you involved with such a girl?!
It wasn't my intention.
She came here.
For what?
I thought that she would give me my money back....
You lent her money?!
You got your money back?
She took more.
What are you doing.
Anyway, don't see her again.
Uh...I guess.
What is this inarticulate answer?!
I told her that I help her find a job.
When I leave her alone, she's probably in a terrible situation.
Even so, why you...
I got involved in her life by fate...
...I think that I have an obligation to help her.
No, you don't. How can you give attention to another girl?
Um? Who is the other girl?
Well...
That's enough!
How was the audition?
Would I look like this if they had chosen me?
Then, I'll treat you to something.
I got 5,000 yen, let's have fun!
How did you get 5,000 yen? You have a boyfriend now?
It's from a man, but....
(Yabe Norio, owner of the Bar Rybeus)
(Yabe Norio, owner of Bar Rybeus)
Ah!
Long time no see.
You're still alive.
Same to you.
Who is this?
Ah, we had a little...before, right?
This and that.
You mean your ex-girlfriend?
I guess so.
I had no idea I was your girlfriend.
I guess not.
You don't have any relationship with her now, right?
Nope. Good bye.
Since we met again, let's go eat.
You just ate, didn't you?
Ah, right.
Come on.
I recently opened a bar nearby...
...it's called "Rybeus". You should come sometime, okay?
He's still an irresponsible man.
If even you call him "irresponsible", he really must be.
Wait, how about eating?
Good. I guess this is it for today.
The client requested it, but he didn't expect...
...you would do it. He was really happy.
I will do my best to live up to your enthusiasm.
It's a plesure to work with you.
Same to you.
Excuse me.
Ah, she is here.
This is the person I was talking about on the phone.
Ah, yes, yes.
This is the interior designer Yamaguchi-san who helps us a lot.
Greeting.
Ah, hi.
Don't you have a better greeting?
I'm sorry.
Are you really sure? I don't know...
...if she will be useful or not.
Ah, it's okay.
An assistant designer suddenly quit...
...I appreciate that you quickly found someone new.
I'm here, you will be fine.
Good!
Excuse us.
Listen, from now on, he will be helping us at work...
...so make sure that you won't be rude to him.
I get it.
Do you really?
I'm sorry to interrupt you, but would you start helping me?
Sure.
Then come here. Well...
...this is what I'm working on right now...
...there is a table and chairs, right?
Excuse me. I'm leaving now.
Okay.
Thanks! See you.
-So casual.
-The fabric that sofa set needs...
Oh, Matsushima-kun.
What is it?
You should know?
Will you come in?
I was just passing by.
I didn't want to bother you at work.
That's fine. Keep going.
What was that?
It's Matsushima.
Were you the one who introduced...
...Kurita Narumi to Yamaguchi-sensei?
Huh? Did she bungle something?
If it were just that!
What?!
She tried to steal money from Yamaguchi-sensei's office...
...and was arrested.
Here you go.
Thank you.
[Yamazaki]
Here they are.
Wow! They look nice.
Are you sure that we can have them?
(Yamazaki Tamami, wife of sales manager Yamazaki)
Oh, please.
I told our mother that we have no need, but she keeps sending them.
Then I will have them. Thank you.
Yamaguchi-sensei...
...dropped the lawsuit against her.
For future businesses...
...he doesn't intend to ask you to be responsible either.
Yes.
Master...
(Yamazaki Ryosuke, son of sales manager Yamazaki)
...teach me Judo.
I'm sorry, maybe next time.
Why don't you help mom.
Yeees.
Ah, Ryo-kun.
I will help you.
Okay, then...
...take these chopsticks.
She keeps silence at the police station.
Looks like she accepts her guilt.
I'm really sorry.
You didn't have a close relationship with her?
Of course not. I had only a litte bit to do with her.
Then forget about her.
Yes.
Ah, that's the awful woman you talked about the other day.
Don't listen to someone else's conversation.
You should not see her again.
You are naive, so you are easily deceived.
I don't want you to tell me that.
She is worried about you, right?
Anyway, like your sister said, don't get close to her.
That's what I intend to do.
We are worried too.
Because we are like parents to you.
Well, dinner is ready.
Okay.
Thank you.
It's such an honor...
...to be assigned as a custodian.
There is nobody else.
How about the friend that you live with?
I can't cause her trouble any more.
You can even be considerate sometimes.
Welcome. Welcome. Please enjoy your stay.
So, how long are you staying at your friend's place?
She told me to leave.
Then you can come to my place anytime.
Huh? How about the woman from the other day?
Ah, her. That's over. I got dumped.
After all, I think that you are the best.
I will pass that on. But I appreciate it for today.
You aren't satisfied with normal men, right?
In the end, man and woman are...
In the end what?
I don't know.
I would figure it out if we go out again.
Good bye.
Aren't you pinched for money?
I borrowed money from someone. I will bring it back.
Well, let's get going.
You don't need to come.
The sales manager asked me to.
Hide, we will go apologize to Yamaguchi-sensei.
Yes.
Matsushima-san.
The girl came here again.
How she can come here.
Where?
She already left.
She wanted to pass this on to you.
Where did she go?
How should I know?!
Damn it.
Thanks for waiting.
What time is your audition?
11 o'clock.
I will be waiting outside, so you don't get nervous.
Hold on!
What is this?
The money I borrowed.
How did you get this money?
I didn't steal it.
I don't need my money back, and I don't want you to come anymore.
What do you mean?
I was wrong about you.
I thought that you were a better person.
We promised that since he will be helping us...
...make sure to not be rude to him.
Is there something more rude than stealing his money?
Say something!
Do you think that you are always right?
Huh?
Hey!
She is an irresponsible person, but she would not steal money.
She was attacked by this Yamaguchi.
What?
Narumi pushed him away.
Then he claimed that Narumi stole his money...
...and called the police.
Is that true?
Then just tell me.
Look!
Did you tell him something unnecessary?
Kinda.
Ah, thanks for waiting.
We are terribly sorry about this.
Well, I do business with your company...
...so I thought that I should settle it peacefully this time.
Ah, have a seat.
Thank you, sir.
We really appreciate that...
...you settled it peacefully.
Well, in the end, my money was not stolen anyway...
...and nobody will benefit from the trouble.
Thank you very much.
Even today, you didn't need to...
...come all the way here for that.
No, we can't be like that.
Anyway, you two should also be prudent...
...about a woman like her.
She has a cute face, but she's a slut.
I don't know what young people are up to nowadays.
Well, I have work to do, so excuse me?
Yes.
Excuse me...
I would like to ask you one thing.
What is it?
Is it true that you tried to push her down?
Hey!
What are you saying?
Is it true?
What do you mean...
What are you talking about?
As a joke this is too much.
Please answer me.
For me this project is important!
Stop it.
Is it true?
Please tell me the truth.
Let's leave it as it is for both of us.
Then you did it!
If so, then what?
You are going to screw up your work for that woman?
If I step down from this project, it won't work out.
You know that, right?
That's right. You stop it now.
The project's success is more important for the company.
You want this project to succeed and advance your career, right?!
Do you want to ruin your career for such a woman?
Don't make me more angry.
If you do that, I won't keep my mouth shut.
You don't care about your position at the company, huh?
You are....
Maybe, she knew what to expect by working here.
That's why she didn't say anything to the police.
You are wrong!
Don't you know how the woman you tried to attack...
...felt and why she kept silent at the police station?
Why do you think she could not say anything?
It's true that you are an excellent designer.
But you are wrong.
Hey, Matsushima.
I don't care if the company does business with you.
But I can't work with you.
Excuse me.
I'm sorry about that. I will talk to the company.
Kenichiro!
I see. So where did Matsushima go?
Anyway, you should come back here.
What?
Sorry.
Because I introduced him to you...
...I have hurt you.
It's all right.
No, it's not.
You could not say anything even to the police, right?
Yeah.
You must have suffered. I am sorry.
A woman cannot talk about such a thing.
Yeah, I cannot.
If I confessed, I'ld go to jail.
Huh?
I was so nervous that they would find out.
Did you... take the money?
I would never take the money!
I took this.
Huh? From Yamaguchi-san's office?
The old man tried to push me down...
...so I kicked him back.
In this moment, an employee came back to the office, so...
...he started to make a fuss that I tried to steal his money...
...and he even called the police.
((She tried to take money from my desk.))
I got pissed, so I took this in the commotion.
((Tell them that she conducted violence.))
((Yes, I got it.))
That's from 1980. It must be tens of thousands of yen?!
That much? Lucky!
I know a bar owner, I can sell it to him.
You... give it back.
It's fine and too late anyways.
It's not fine!
Fine!
Let go.
You let go!
Let go!
Return it!
What a waste!
I guess we have to compensate him.
If you keep quiet he won't know.
I don't like it that way.
Are you stupid?
I'm fine being stupid!
If this one's also expensive?
For that reason, Matsushima has been dropped from this project...
...and would do field work for a while.
So, you have been transferred from the main office?!
If you did something bad, do it better next time.
I am...
Damn it!
I will live a straightforward life.
I will!
Lucky!
Yummy.
Hey!
Don't dig straight!
Bend here.
I'm sorry.
I'll put it back.
Help me please.Come quickly.
Do you have an obligation to help her?
I can't neglect someone who needs help.
Because you want to protect Narumi-san?
He is up to something.
Just get Matsushima here!
Please become a Buddha.
Wouldn't you mind...
...opening your hearts a little bit?
I need to talk to you.